(Howard:)Ow! Damn. Paper cut.
Nothing worse than a paper cut.
(Raj:)Well, obviously,
you don't remember your circumcision.
(Sheldon:)There's Neosporin and Band-Aids
in my top desk drawer.
(Howard:)Why don't you keep that stuff
in the bathroom?
(Leonard:)He does. And in the kitchen,
and in the car, and in his pocket.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but the ones in my pocket
are mine.
(Scene:)-Hi.
-Hey.
Guess who's gonna be
at the comic store on Thursday.
(Penny:)-Um, can you give me a hint?
-Stan Lee.
(Penny:)Um, Stanley. Stanley. Stanley Tucci?
No, ha, ha. No. Stan Lee.
Oh. Oh, Stan Lee. Cool.
[CHUCKLES]
(Leonard:)You have no idea who he is, do you?
(Penny:)Of course I do.
You're an important part of my life...
(Penny:)...and I pay attention to the things
you are interested in.
(Leonard:)-Good. Good.
-Heh, heh.
(Leonard:)So who's Stan Lee?
(Penny:)Um, he was on Star Trek.